Subtitles by explosiveskull
In the Bay of Naples, a few kilometers
from Pompeii and Vesuvius,
lies the world's most surprising
underwater archeological site.
Here is the lost Roman city of Baia.
Since the first century BC
it has been an exclusive place...
See the lovely parmigiana
Mom made for you?
Patrizia, will you tell me
what's the matter?
Last night I saw
a documentary about bees.
The males do nothing
from morning till night.
They only wake up
when the Queen sends for them.
They mate in flight for safety.
And they fuck so much
that their balls explode.
And then they die.
One after another,
'cause they're no good
for anything anymore.
That's all they can do.
From the samples you brought from Milan,
I see you do elegant stuff.
What's the retail price? 1,200?
You sell them to retailers at 500 max.
Once you buy fabric,
pay seamstresses, packing, shipping,
you're left with 10%, right?
Right.
Go with us
and your earnings will triple.
And how?
Our labor costs are low:
two or three euros an hour.
It depends what their work's like.
You only have to decide, Evelina.
You can work with subcontractors
in your area that cost more
and won't do an hour of overtime
for love or money,
or you can make real money with us.
- The paper pattern?
- I only have them for the samples.
- You'll do patterns and size-charts.
- No problem... Fabric?
I'll courier it all to you tomorrow.
- Dad, I got A in math!
- Well done!
What's the matter?
- You take a bath in perfume?
- You don't like it?
I like it, on a woman, though.
Let's go wash our hands,
dinner is ready.
Well done, Daddy's little scholar.
How did the checkup go?
Is the baby growing?
- Everything's good.
- And Patrizia?
She decided to have a rest.
Good, if only
she'd give it a rest for real.
What's happening
in Central Naples is no good,
and if the problem spreads
it'll weaken Secondigliano.
And to keep helping a weak clan
is too risky.
I don't think Patrizia's fit
to rule right now.
You're her husband,
make her see reason.
Now she has two options:
be a woman or a commander.
I'd like to know
what it is that you want,
if you want to raise a kid
or you want to mourn your wife.
Now let's eat, I'm starved.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Ghost.
Lord, bless this food.
Our Father...
Who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name...
The Levantes are behind the bust.
They want to take Secondigliano.
They blamed Nicola and killed him.
Now they're hand in hand
with the Graduate,
who took everything
that was Blue Blood's.
My husband's one of them, Gennaro.
And you didn't notice
anything, Patrizia?
I told you: a boss can never
trust anyone.
- I know.
- Doesn't look like it.
What are you going to do?
I can only do two things.
Be a wife and mother and leave
everything to the Levantes.
Or I wipe out every last one of them.
I handed over a kingdom to you.
Mine, the Savastanos'.
And you're still here
asking me which way to go.
No, Gennaro.
You're wrong.
I just wanted you to know.
This is my house.
And in my house I call the shots.
OUR BROTHERS
You're nuts coming here.
You know the Capaccios
run Forcella now.
Since you killed his brother,
the Graduate's looking all over for you.
I could have put it here for you.
I'm the one who needs to be pardoned.
I know what you're risking,
Pure'n'Simple,
but you gotta set up a meeting
for me with our most trusted guys.
You got it.
How do you feel?
I managed to get some rest.
I had to make a decision
before talking to you.
And I've made it.
I have to think about
our Bianca first.
It's best if I hand over the command
of Secondigliano to you.
Bianca?
That was my mother's name.
We'll do whatever you want, sweetheart.
This place is like a jail.
But if Patrizia hadn't given us
a crash pad, by now we'd be dead.
I don't want to mourn you.
I can't stop now.
First I gotta avenge our brothers.
You building a tower?
Things aren't going well, Azzurra.
Secondigliano's about to blow up.
- That's not our problem.
- Yes, it is.
When things are going well,
we're all friends.
But when things get outta balance,
who knows what could happen.
You put Patrizia there, for a reason:
to buy us our freedom.
I hadn't heard the news.
Congratulations.
- Thank you. So, how are things?
- Good.
Igor, for the moment, I can't
personally handle the shipments.
My husband Michelangelo
will handle them.
Talk to him like you talk to me.
One.
Gimme twenty.
Morning, Don Michelangelo. Please.
We're done here, Donna Patrizia.
It's 213 grand.
In line with last week,
maybe a bit more.
This isn't a neighborhood.
It's a city within a bigger city.
Secondigliano doesn't answer to anyone.
Enzo came to me.
He loathes everyone.
He says that your family's
behind the bust
and now he asks for my help.
He wants to kill you all.
Why didn't you tell me straightaway?
Because I had doubts.
About me?
Yeah.
And now it's gone?
No.
But I've made a choice.
Enzo's here...
But you gotta make me a promise.
You gotta make a choice,
like I did, and remove all doubt.
Enzo...
What have you done, bro'?
Check out the hair.
Hey, Enzo.
I'm glad to see you.
Patrizia and I have
the same enemy: the Levantes.
First they used
the Capaccios like puppets,
then they took our turf.
We gotta hide to talk.
They better not think
I've forgotten them.
I think about them all the time.
Night and day...
All the time.
What do you got in mind, Enzo?
Patrizia just wants to be a mom.
She's made up her mind.
And she's handed everything over to me.
Shipping, dealing spots...
Secondigliano.
She handed it over to me, Dad,
not to you.
You never liked this place.
You never came here to work,
but our family's fortune starts here.
Michelangelo...
To make concrete
you need to mix sand with cement.
And what comes out is a new substance,
that belongs to us,
it belongs to our family.
You and Patrizia are like
sand and cement.
You've become a substance
that can build something very big.
And if you understand it,
so does she.
You're right, Dad.
There's something else
we have to settle.
We have to kill Blue Blood.
- Well?
- It's good, I like it.
Thanks for coming, guys.
They told us you'd retired.
Maybe it's time for me
to get back to work.
We missed you, Don Gennaro.
Let's go.
Go, go!
There's no one here.
Run, it's a trap! Sons of bitches!
You pieces of shit!
Guys, after him!
Mom?
I'm fine, why? What's happened?
Calm down, Mom.
What are you saying?
And how are they?
The main thing is that they're okay.
I'll be right there.
We failed.
Good evening, Don Gennaro.
Mistral's sorry,
but he couldn't come to the meeting.
- He sent his regards.
- Don't worry about it.
I know what it means
to live on high alert.
With all due respect,
we thought you'd retired
from our business.
Or am I wrong?
It's true.
But now I've got money,
contacts and skills.
Above all, I need to take back
everything that's mine.
Excuse me, if you'll allow me...
Can I ask you something Mistral
would have asked for sure?
Go ahead.
Why did you choose him?
The next war's gonna be long and hard.
And a man who had the guts to eat
his enemy's heart in prison
is a man who'll do anything.
And I need someone like that
to win this war.
But that's water under the bridge.
After that, he did 20 years
of maximum security
and his friends all turned
their backs on him.
I know.
But I also know that he once had
enormous ambition
and that's something that never dies.
Subtitles by explosiveskull