Subtitles by explosiveskull
LONDON
- Hi, Alberto.
- Hi.
- Did you call your friend?
- First thing I did.
- What did she say?
- It's all set up.
Leena will get it done, you'll see.
I've known her for 15 years,
she's a Mack truck.
Now she's gone into business
with a genius of finance
and I checked their acquisitions
over recent years, all blue chip.
Thank you.
Gennaro, you need to relax.
I need to relax, Alberto?
All I know is until a few days ago
everything was going well,
now if I don't buy an international
company in two weeks,
like fuck I'll open the airport.
That's not a good thing,
neither for me nor for you.
Don't ever forget that.
Hello?
Good.
They've arrived.
Get it done now,
we don't have a minute to lose.
- See you here in an hour.
- Right.
Hello.
Gennaro Savastano.
Ah, Mr. Savastano.
Our bank manager, Mr. Cormack
is waiting for you.
Mr. Savastano,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
This way, please.
So, Mr. Savastano...
You put in your personal code,
and here is your key card.
If you need anything else, let me know.
Thank you.
Hello.
- Thank you.
- Leena!
- Alberto!
I'm so glad to see you.
This is the person
I told you about,
my partner, Mr. Gennaro Savastano.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Please sit down.
- Do you want something? A coffee?
- No, thank you.
I found what you asked for.
Or rather, my partner, Patrick did.
He's fantastic.
But, given the short notice,
it wasn't easy.
In the end, we were lucky.
Anyway...
I'm sure that you're in a hurry,
so... shall we go?
Patrick's waiting for us at the office
with more details.
- He said that Patrick...
- I understood.
Let's go.
It's this-this way.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Patrick...
Patrick Calvis, it's a pleasure.
Gennaro Savastano.
- Patrick.
- Alberto Resta,
- Pleasure.
- Nice to meet you.
Please come in, take a seat.
- Can I get anyone a coffee?
- No, thank you, Leena.
Yes, please.
Harry?
So Leena tells me you've just
a couple of weeks to close the deal.
Let's get straight to the point, sir.
Wimpro.
Market value: £20 million.
The price is not an issue.
Well... well, Patrick...
But...
if it's so, why do they need to sell?
In the past year,
Wimpro made some bad investments.
Not through it's own fault,
now, they've been exposed and
they need to close a contract ASAP.
But...
they haven't got the money
to do so all by themselves.
So, apparently...
Wimpro need you
more than you need them.
We just have to let them know.
Now, it's up to you.
Did you get that
or do I have to translate?
Well? How's it going?
For the moment, everything's okay.
Here's Gaetano.
- Who's that?
- A person who works for me in London.
- Welcome, Mrs. Savastano.
- Thank you.
Do you think it's good?
We have to go home
with an international company
to head up the consortium
or else Casillo's friend won't give us
the contract for the airport.
So you've already decided?
- For you, madam.
- Thank you.
And for you, sir.
- You're welcome.
They asked me
to make an irrevocable bid.
An irrevocable bid?
And I did.
This city has always
made me feel anxious.
Me too.
- Is everything okay?
- Not really.
- We have a problem.
- What's happened?
The owners, the Mayers family
have asked for a partners meeting.
It's starting as we speak.
We're going to try to get the others
to reject your offer.
The owners want to reject the offer.
- Can they do that?
- If they convince the majority, yes.
Patrick's there already.
You need to try to convince them.
My car's waiting outside.
It's here.
Go to the back entrance.
You're not allowed
into the shareholders meeting.
We can't walk in the front door.
Apparently, the meeting
hasn't started yet.
It'll be a couple of minutes.
Did you see those
two men I was talking to?
- Mm-hmm.
- They are the men we need to persuade.
They belong to the
anti-Mayers faction.
They claim the Mayers'
management has damaged the business.
They hold 7% and 5% respectively.
They can convince the other 39%
to sell to you.
- So we need them on our side.
- Definitely.
Azzurra?
I sent you a message
with the instructions.
Gaetano is coming to get you.
- Haven't they arrived yet?
- No. Did you bring them?
- They're here. Good morning, Alberto.
- Good morning.
- Want a coffee?
- No.
It's disgusting anyway.
- Good afternoon.
- Hello, Leena.
Hello.
John Millivan, Bernard Edgewood.
Please, have a seat.
I'd like to present Alberto Resta,
Gennaro Savastano
and Azzurra Avitabile.
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleasure to meet you.
So...
our project...
is to build the biggest airport
ever built on Italian soil.
Yours...
is to get rid of... of the leadership
who doesn't go anywhere.
What do you think about?
Be practical.
We know your business
is in trouble.
If you don't close a contract
in the next few months,
you risk going bankrupt
and losing everything.
On the other hand,
we have the opportunity to close
one of the biggest
infrastructure projects in Italy.
But to do so,
we need a company like yours.
It's a win-win situation.
You just have to say yes.
And convince your associates...
to accept our offer.
It's not for free...
of course.
I've spoken to the board.
You are, now, the majority owner.
They have accepted your bid.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations, Alberto.
- Thank you.
You're already up?
I'll help you.
I'm proud of you, Gennaro.
See you later at the office?
Well?
Good one, Gaetano.
I'll be right down.
Everything is fine.
It's done.
It's real now.
Leena, could you send us all
the documents by mail today please?
We need them for our associates
for a fast check.
- Of course. Leena, you can do that?
- Of course.
Thank you.
Michele. We did it.
The paperwork's on its way to you,
check immediately that it's all okay,
before we go to the notary.
I need to know straightaway.
Thanks.
Cheers!
Check this out, Alberto.
- What is it?
- Dunno.
Looks good, though.
It's Casillo.
Michele.
I can't hear you.
Now I can.
What?
I'll take care of it now.
What did he say?
There's a document missing,
the banks' approval
for the transfer of ownership.
Wimpro has three lines of credit
with three different banks.
They have to give permission
when ownership changes.
But it's a formality,
they must have forgotten.
I'll call Leena,
they'll be at the office.
Her phone's switched off, that's odd.
I'll try Patrick.
Put your shoes on.
Patrick's is switched off, too...
It'll be quicker to go in person.
Be careful, Azzurra.
I called Wimpro's headquarters.
They don't know who we are,
they've never even heard of us.
It was all fake.
Gennaro, that's not possible.
I've known Leena for 15 years,
she's always been legit.
I checked her company:
the accounts, acquisitions, contracts.
There has to be another explanation.
There's shit everywhere,
it just has different colors.
There's your explanation.
We have two advantages,
the first is that they weren't
expecting us to find out so soon,
the second is that I know more
than they think.
Gennaro, I swear,
I'm not involved.
I know you're not,
but do me a favor.
Whatever you want.
From now on, just keep
that fucking mouth of yours shut.
Let's go.
- Hello.
Hello, momma.
I found the Grevillea.
How are you to...
Please don't hurt her.
See, Ma'am? Leena's here.
Please.
Only I knew. I could feel it.
That's why I had you followed
the other night.
I've fucking had it with this game!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm really...
We're all so predictable, so petty.
We all have someone important
we'd do anything for,
even something really fucking stupid.
I knew you couldn't leave without
saying goodbye to your mom.
Right, Leena?
Where is my gold?
It's...
in the warehouse.
But I don't have a key.
And where is the key?
I don't have it. I don't have it.
No?
Patrick...
Check there.
What the fuck have you done?
Is he dead?
- Yes.
- I needed him alive, asshole!
Go and see if anyone's coming.
The piece.
Motherfuckers...
We gotta make him disappear.
Take the arms, hurry.
Our gold is here.
If we hadn't made it in time
tonight it was headed to Singapore.
Come, Gaetano.
See, there's a door.
Is the gold there?
Leena...
Love makes people act crazy.
Now that I've found my gold,
I'm happier,
so I'll give you another chance.
Untie her.
I came to London
because I had a problem
and now you have to solve it for me
unless you wanna end up
like your friend.
You have 36 hours,
Gaetano will be your shadow.
You understand?
Alberto, come here.
Come here!
Translate.
Come,
let's call them straightaway.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I really missed
our little lamb chop so much.
I missed him, too.
I really missed
being in my own home.
But now we're back
and we have the company we needed.
In the end, Alberto was right,
Leena was really useful.
Subtitles by explosiveskull