Subtitles by explosiveskull
Thank you.
After 30 years
of announcements and empty talk,
this evening we are gathered here
to celebrate among friends,
because the second airport hub
for Naples is no longer a dream,
it is about to become reality.
Firstly, I'd like to thank our hostess,
a great woman.
The woman who currently
leads this consortium,
Ms Tiziana Palumbo.
The hemorrhage has been
completely reabsorbed.
The amniotic sac is intact, blood-flow
velocity is good. You're lucky.
You can be returned
to the correctional facility.
All right, sir,
she's coming out now.
Mrs Santore, I'll escort you
back to the correctional facility.
- What is it?
- The Levantes tried to clip Patrizia.
She's at the hospital.
- And how is she?
- I don't know.
But she sent us a message
and a request.
- What message?
- She doesn't want to stay in prison.
But she's only got one way to get out.
Ruggieri. And the request?
She wants to know if she's got
a good friend who can get her out,
because she can't hold out much longer.
Thanks, Fernando.
The baby's all right, yeah?
Prison's no place for a woman
in your condition.
And who knows
what could happen next time.
I want to speak to him.
What are you doing in the dark, Gennaro?
How did it go?
Michele says hi.
He dedicated his speech to us.
And you? Any news?
Patrizia got the message.
And?
She just asked for a lawyer,
she wants the best.
We've discussed this already.
You don't need to worry.
Patrizia won't talk.
I'll tell you whatever you want to know,
but I have to get out now.
I'm glad you've taken this decision.
But let's make one thing clear:
you're not doing me any favors.
I represent the state
and the state has rules and procedures.
Firstly, you are obliged
to tell the truth
and we have 120 days to verify
whether what you say
is baloney or true.
And in those 120 days
your condition can't change.
I can't go back to prison.
Maybe there is a way.
What do you say, Biagio?
A spontaneous statement
that can lead to a sure conviction.
Annalisa Maiocca.
- Do you know who she is?
- Yes.
We know that she's been missing
for almost two years.
She vanished from the face of the earth
because I killed her.
Good morning.
Wait in the car.
- How's Patrizia?
- Pardon?
- Have I done something to you?
- You've got the wrong idea.
And what's the right idea?
I like to win,
I've always been competitive.
Maybe I hoped my father would
come back for a son who's a winner.
My father only ever wanted one thing...
for me to be like him.
But I've never been like him.
And when I was younger
it made me feel bad.
But then you know what I realized?
That there are things I can do well....
and other things I just can't do.
I wouldn't worry too much.
From what I know
and from what people tell me about you,
I'm sure your father would be
very proud of you.
Good morning, Giancarlo Presti,
court-appointed counsel.
Good morning.
Why didn't you include your husband
in the protective measures?
You can save his life.
He decided about my life without asking,
the consequences are not my problem.
You're about to have a baby,
don't you want him by your side?
He'd need to forget who he was,
break with his family.
Only he can decide if he wants that.
- Can we start?
- Sure.
Wait here.
Hi, Uncle.
What brings you here again, Gennaro?
- You know very well.
- You have to tell me.
Patrizia will talk.
She hasn't yet,
but I've got to be quick.
And what do you want from me?
I have to free her now, they're holding
her at a secret location.
You're the only one who can find her,
and you know it.
Unfortunately they've hidden her
too well and no one can find her.
And even if I could do it, I wouldn't.
I never liked her.
But if she talks
it's a problem for you, too.
Against us there's only her word.
Maybe it's worth making an effort?
The only one shaking things up is her,
and she's one of yours.
But before she shook things,
her house got shook up.
- And it wasn't me who did that.
- Are you accusing us of something?
My father wanted nothing to do with you,
he said you've always been
poison for this land
and that you would've been ready
to devour him and Secondigliano.
Your father had a lot of faults,
but he knew how to see things.
You don't. And he knew that too.
My father always underestimated me.
The youngest in the family is
Francesco Levante, known as Ciccio.
You telling me this to get revenge?
You asked me what I know,
I know them well.
You know him too, don't you?
- You know the answer.
- No, that's not how depositions work.
You need to tell me in your own words.
Welcome, Don Gennaro.
I'm still waiting for your answer.
Mistral says
he's honored by your offer
and we're happy to give you a hand.
In other words, we're at your disposal.
That's what I wanted to hear.
Let's go, guys.
It took a big effort...
but in the end we did it.
A big effort
and for me it was an honor.
Did something happen?
I gotta ask you something important.
Something I can only ask a friend.
Because that's what you are, Tiziana.
Aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Good.
Whatever happens,
from now on, my dream depends on you.
But you must never let me down.
Write down whatever
basic needs you have,
I'll see that you get them straightaway.
You'll find a change of clothes
in the closet.
For anything, we're here.
Gennaro, are you ready?
- Are you all right?
- Sure.
Then let's go.
You're so beautiful.
When you married me you gave me
the most beautiful gift in the world.
I tried to be the man you deserved,
the father you wanted for Pietro.
And you succeeded.
I don't know, but I tried.
I tried very hard.
I did it for you two
and for my brother Ciro,
who died to leave us with his dream.
But in this new life
I felt a battle inside me.
And what I was before began pounding,
wanting to get out again.
It hasn't come out, though.
Remember one thing.
What, Gennaro?
All the dreams we have for Pietro
will come true, I promise you.
And the battle?
The battle's over.
I heard about your brother.
The peace you sold us was bullshit.
Peace doesn't kill people.
But it's not made for people like us.
Did you bring my friend?
And where's my present?
You'll get it before I leave here.
Patrizia asked me to help her escape.
And why did she ask you and not me?
Do I have to explain it?
Anyway, I can't do it alone.
You know what it means?
You got one last chance to show
your wife what side you're on.
And what do I have to do?
You gotta help me find out
where the cops have taken her.
And after that?
After that you gotta tell the Graduate
where Enzo's hiding.
Pure'n'Simple, what's going on?
Enzo, wait!
Trust me, listen to him.
And what can a rat tell me?
The Graduate's on the move.
He called all his men,
but he didn't tell us anything.
And so?
I think they're coming after you,
they know where you are.
- Why you telling me this?
- 'Cause I made a mistake.
And I also want to be forgiven.
Don't move, you pieces of shit.
What the fuck are you doing?
Where's Enzo?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him for days.
Enzo...
Enzo, we gotta go.
We gotta go!
Enzo...
We gotta go. Guys, we gotta go!
Sorry I'm late.
- It was you who got Patrizia arrested.
- Yes.
Why did you do it?
- You didn't leave me any choice.
- You had a choice, Michelangelo.
And you didn't choose us.
That's why you're nothing to us anymore.
Excuse me, Dad.
I came to say goodbye.
But first I wanted to thank you, Dad,
because if family's
the most important thing for me,
it's because you taught me that.
As far as I can see,
you didn't learn it very well.
You're wrong.
You and I are more similar
than you think.
Goodbye, Mom.
Just a moment.
Come in.
We've been informed
your husband wishes to collaborate.
- And they're bringing him here?
- Exactly.
Ruggieri says that as soon as
you finish the depositions,
you'll sign the statement and you'll
have new identities and residence.
Thank you.
I wanna kill that filthy bitch
with my own two hands!
What the fuck's going on?
Take a message to your brothers.
Gennaro Savastano is back.
Yes.
We gotta go,
for anything you need
my colleagues are here.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
How are you both?
Good.
The second escort has left.
Let's roll.
Thank you, Gennaro.
- Is it for us?
- Yes.
Where's it going?
Faraway, that way we'll all be safer.
- Patrizia, can I have a word?
- Of course.
See you up there.
Goodbye, Gennaro.
Goodbye, Michelangelo.
Well?
- This is your dream?
- It was.
The truth is, for people like us
dreams don't exist.
What will you do now?
Tally up who are friends
and who are enemies.
I gotta make up for all my mistakes.
You made a big one: Gerlando.
I've already taken care of it.
The next one is the prosecutor.
- What did you tell him?
- I talked about myself.
Didn't he ask you about me?
No, he didn't ask me anything.
Help me to believe you, Patrizia.
You know my story.
You know where I come from,
I never asked anybody for anything.
I never kneeled down
and I don't want to start now.
I'd never betray you and you know it.
You feel it inside.
That should be enough.
Remember when I told you
never to trust anyone?
I never told you not to trust me either.
Is this it, Gennaro?
This is it, Patrizia.
Don Gennaro, come with me.
Subtitles by explosiveskull